<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contributings on Apache Celix</title>
    <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contributings on Apache Celix</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://celix.apache.org/contributing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Development workflow</title>
      <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/development-workflow.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/development-workflow.html</guid>
      <description>Development workflow Celix uses an adapted version of the GitFlow workflow. The default branch of the Celix repositories is the master branch. Feature branches are created from and against the master branch. Releases &amp;amp; hotfixes are also created from and against the master branch.
The following image visualizes the workflow Celix is using:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Releasing Process</title>
      <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/releasing.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/releasing.html</guid>
      <description>Releasing Apache Celix Note: This information is only of use to Apache Celix Release Managers!
Steps to follow:
 Create signing KEYS Create release branch Update release related files Compile and test Create, sign and publish artifacts Run the vote Post the vote results Vote Passed  Create Git tag and merge to master Roll out release artifacts Publish release documentation Update the website Announce the release     Interesting links:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Source code and builds</title>
      <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/source-and-builds.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/source-and-builds.html</guid>
      <description>Source code and builds  Celix source repository  Building and using Celix   Website source repository  Building the website     Celix source repository Besides the archives offered on the download page, Celix uses a source code repository hosted on both Apache and GitHub environments for development. This repository is mirrored and is our one-and-only development repository.
With Git installed, obtaining a working copy of the Celix codebase is as simple as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submitting patches</title>
      <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/submitting-patches.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/submitting-patches.html</guid>
      <description>Submitting patches  Contributing with GitHub Committers Further reading   Celix uses Git so you must install a git client locally to be able to clone the Celix repository. The development workflow that Apache Celix is following is described here. Contributing with GitHub Using the GitHub mirror is the simplest way to contribute to Apache Celix if you are not a member of the Celix Committers group.
First you must have an account created at GitHub to be able perform the next step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/volunteers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/volunteers.html</guid>
      <description>Volunteers  Project Management Committee Members Committers   The project consists of a diverse group of volunteers who share common values regarding collaborative, community-based open source development.
Project Management Committee Members Committee members are listed in the chronological order, according to the date each person became a committee member.
 Alexander Broekhuis (abroekhuis at apache.org) Marcel Offermans (marss at apache.org) Konstantin I Boudnik (cos at apache.org) Pepijn Noltes (pnoltes at apache.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You at Celix</title>
      <link>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/youatcelix.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://celix.apache.org/contributing/youatcelix.html</guid>
      <description>You at Apache Celix We are happy you are considering to contribute to Apache Celix and we are definitely looking forward to your work.
We all are a happy group of volunteers and much often work on Celix in our free time. We are not getting any money for our work from the Apache Software Foundation (nor does any other project receive money) and most of us are not paid by a company for working on Celix.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>